Skúli Arnarsson

Looking for a full time job in web, software or app development

General information

SSN: 280995-2079

Address: Maríubakki 28,109 Reykjavík

Email: skuliarnarsson@gmail.com

Mobile: 858-7111

Personal page: skulia15.github.io GitHub: github.com/skulia15

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/skulipardus



About me

I am a 25 year old student at the University of Reykjavík studying computer science with a focus on web development and user interface design. My interests include everything related to technology, programming, alternative and electronic music, video games, exploring the world and experiencing different cultures. I'm a responsible and an extremely reliable employee. I am quick at learning and mastering new technologies and I like working alongside others in a team. I am most interested in working in web- or app development. I am healthy and don't smoke. I don't have a criminal record. I have a driver's licence and I own a car. I am fully willing to relocate.

Education

Reykjavík University – BSc Computer Science

August 2015 - December 2018, GPA 8.74

BSc in computer science with a focus on web development and user interface design.

Universidad Carlos III de Madrid (Exchange student)— BSc Computer Science

January 2017 - June 2017

Menntaskólinn við Hamrahlíð – Diploma(Stúdentspróf) from gymnasia

August 2011 - May 2015 GPA 8.90

Programming languages

- Javascript
- C#
- Python
- C++
- Java
- C
- SOL
- (HTML5)
- (CSS3)

Tools and technologies

- Vue.is
- React.is
- Xamarin
- Node.is
- **Express**
- ASP.NET
- RESTful web services
- .NET Framework
- Webpack
- Mocha
- Bookshelf.js











Work experience

Advania — Software Specialist

January 2018 - June 2018

Contracting work for OR (Reykjavík Energy). Developing a variety of internal and external systems. Most of my focus has been spent on web programming and integration. Technologies include Vue.js, React and .NET.

//Jökulá, Advertising Agency- Internship

January 2018 - June 2018

My final Project for University of Reykjavík. We build a "Full Stack" web service / application from scratch. The web service is meant for in-house use at Jökulá . The web service handles allocation, supervision and record keeping for all of Jökulá's projects. The service is implemented using *Node.js* for back end functionality and the front end is implemented using *Vue.js*.

Straumhvörf – Night guard / Standard employee

June 2017 - January 2018

I worked part-time both as a night guard and as a standard employee. The job involved care for people who suffer from serious mental disorders.

Te & Kaffi — Barista

September 2014 - December 2017

I worked part-time as a barista. The job involved working the register, making coffee- and tea based drinks, washing dishes, cleaning and I prepared and waited food. I did everything needed to keep a coffeehouse up and running.

NFMH, Students association of Menntaskólans við Hamrahlíð – *Member of marketing committee*

January 2014 - May 2015

I was responsible for the acquisition of sponsorships and advertisements in collaboration with various companies to finance the students association.

ISS Iceland— Delivery driver

May 2014 - September 2014

I worked as a delivery driver for a summer. I drove around the capital area and delivered clean laundry to various companies and organizations. I also oversaw orders and maintenance in the warehouse I also did various other work in the laundry room.

ISS Iceland— Cleaner / Custodian

December 2009 - May 2014

I mostly worked with cleaning in a mall. I worked full-time in the summer and over Christmas, but otherwise I worked two days a week.

- Pug
- Less
- Gulp
- Bootstrap
- Gi
- Agile Methodologies
- Istanbul
- Bash

Languages

Icelandic- Native language

English- Fluent

Spanish, Danish- Working knowledge

French, Italian- Little working knowledge

Grants

Freshmen grant from Reykjavík University - For excellent performance in gymnasia.

Erasmus+ grant - For participating in an Erasmus exchange program in Madrid.







ISS Iceland — Cleaner

May 2013 - August 2013

I worked a summer job in public household services for older people and people with reduced mobility in Gardabær. I managed company vehicle.

Fint slf — Cleaner

December 2009 - May 2014

General cleaning, mopping and waxing floors. I worked part-time with school.

Morgunblaðið — Newspaper carrier

February 2007 - September 2007

I delivered newspapers every day of the week.

References

Gísli Rúnar Sævarsson - Owner at Fínt shf.

Phone: 6649099.

Email: gislirun@gmail.com.

Rakel Róbertsdóttir- Director at Straumhvörf.

Phone: 695-8501.

Jónína Gunnarsdóttir - Service representative at ISS.

Phone: 6964924. Email: jonina@iss.is.









Academic record at Reykjavík University

| Course | | Date | ECTS | Grade | Rank |
|------------|--|------------|-------------|-------------|-------------|
| T-107-TOLH | Computer Architecture | 06.11.2015 | 6 | 9,5 | 30-55/228 |
| T-111-PROG | Programming | 06.11.2015 | 6 | 9,0 | 28-48/190 |
| T-114-VERK | Problem Solving | 16.11.2015 | 6 | 9,0 | 60-123/251 |
| T-117-STR1 | Discrete Mathematics I | 19.11.2015 | 6 | 8,0 | 23-36/173 |
| T-113-VLN1 | Semester Project 1 | 31.12.2015 | 6 | 8,5 | 184-221/262 |
| T-216-GHOH | Software Requirements and Design | 11.04.2016 | 6 | 9,0 | 13-34/224 |
| T-419-STR2 | Discrete Mathematics II | 14.04.2016 | 6 | 9,0 | 27-50/153 |
| T-201-GSKI | Data Structures | 18.04.2016 | 6 | 8,0 | 63-86/204 |
| T-213-VEFF | Web-Programming | 22.04.2016 | 6 | 9,0 | 33-64/242 |
| T-220-VLN2 | Semester Project 2 | 31.05.2016 | 6 | 8,0 | 150-183/230 |
| T-303-HUGB | Software Engineering | 09.11.2016 | 6 | 8,0 | 52-92/219 |
| T-301-REIR | Algorithms | 15.11.2016 | 6 | 9,0 | 22-40/208 |
| T-202-GAG1 | Databases | 21.11.2016 | 6 | 8,5 | 40-66/222 |
| T-317-CAST | Calculus and Statistics | 24.11.2016 | 6 | 9,0 | 9-17/134 |
| T-308-PRLA | The Python Programming Language | 31.12.2016 | 6 | 8,5 | 34-43/99 |
| T-215-STY1 | Operating Systems | 21.06.2017 | 6 | Transferred | |
| T-513-CRNU | Cryptography and Computer Security | 21.06.2017 | 6 | Transferred | |
| T-622-ARTI | Artificial Intelligence | 21.06.2017 | 6 | Transferred | |
| T-636-SMAT | Human Computer Interaction | 13.11.2017 | 6 | 9,0 | 1-2/19 |
| T-302-HONN | Software Design and Implementation | 14.11.2017 | 6 | 9,5 | 3-5/56 |
| T-514-VEFT | Web Services | 16.11.2017 | 6 | 9,0 | 12-25/93 |
| T-409-TSAM | Computer Networks | 23.11.2017 | 6 | 8,0 | 34-50/172 |
| T-488-MAPP | Mobile App Development | 31.12.2017 | 6 | 9,0 | 5-8/40 |
| T-631-SOE2 | Software Engineering II - Testing | 09.04.2018 | 6 | 9,0 | 10-18/48 |
| T-501-FMAL | Programming Languages | 13.04.2018 | 6 | 8,0 | 26-39/183 |
| T-427-WEPO | Web-Programming II | 20.04.2018 | 6 | 9,5 | 8-11/88 |
| T-404-LOKA | Final Project | 31.05.2018 | 12 | 8,5 | 43-86/129 |
| I-406-IERP | Introduction to ERP Systems | 31.12.2018 | 6 | 8,0 | 36-40/48 |
| T-542-HGOP | Introduction to quality management and testing | 31.12.2018 | 6 | 10,0 | 1-2/33 |

ECTS required for BSc in Computer Science - general: 180





Total ECTS:

Average:

180,00

8,74

